blackberryempire.com 2016-11-03

# Privacy Policy - Blackberry Empire

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

**Do we use cookies?**

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies in a limited way to help deliver advertisements, to identify unique browsers that visit us and to track usage throughout our site.

The information about readership and site usage that BlackBerryEmpire.com collects through cookies is aggregated into general reports about readership and not tied to individual identities.

Other companies which place advertising on our site also have the ability to assign their cookies to you in a process that BlackBerryEmpre.com does not control. However, cookies cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines, so these advertisers will not know who you are.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous  
information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally  
identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and  
date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this  
and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services  
likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or  
third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this  
behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can  
visit networkadvertising.org.  
**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**BlackBerry Empire**

**info@blackberryempire.com**

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [web site privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Unsubscribe and Data  Removal Policies**  
If you would like to remove your name and e-mail address from our registration database, you can send an e-mail requesting removal to info@blackberryempire.com

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

info@blackberryempire.com
